



(+852) 6040 8671



shirau@gmail.com



shirau.github.io/ shirleyau/

EDUCATION

2023

Google UX Design Certificate

Coursera

2006-2008

Multimedia Design & Technology (HD)

Hong Kong Polytechnic University

SKILLS

User Experience

- Persona
- Target Audience Journey
- Information Architecture
- Site Mapping
- Wireframe
- User Flows
- Prototyping
- Quality Assurance
- Usability Testing
- Collaboration with Development Teams

Visual Design

- Mood Board
- Branding
- Interface Design
- Information Design

SHIRLEYAU UX & UI DESIGNER

DIGITAL PRODUCTS. PRINT PRODUCTS

SUMMARY

A seasoned digital product designer with over 10 years of experience designing products across various sectors including retail, education, gaming, bank and digital advertisement business. Proficient in user-centered design processes, specializing in rapid prototyping, interaction design and final user interface visual design. Looking to excel in both analytical and creative thinking, and shape better user experience design.

EXPERIENCE

5.2022 - Present

UX, UI Designer

Konew FinTech Corporation Limited (2483.HK)



Loan System, Personal, Property Loan Mobile Apps, Web Design, Entertainment Platform Design

- As a product designer, conduct ongoing research of user interface development best practices
- Translate user stories/business requirements and build prototypes of proposed features in company products
- Come up with user-centered design solutions with various technology teams (Product, Development, QA, Ops, Innovation, etc.) to understand user needs and business requirements

9.2014 - 4.2022



Advisory Senior UX Designer

iClick Interactive Asia Limited (NASDAQ: ICLK)

B2B Data Analysis Platform, Ad Targeting Platform, Wechat Mini Program, Mobile Ad Landing Webpages

- Build and design prototypes of proposed features in company products
- Come up with user-centered design solutions with teams in Shanghai and Beijing such as project managers and engineers to understand user needs and business requirements
- Collorate with Ctrip on delivering Wechat mini programs to reach out China market
- Online advertisment support: Banner and mobile ad landing page design

1.2014 - 6.2014

UI & UX Designer

nBition Development Limited



Mobile Game Apps, Marketing Materials

- Work closely with the team to design user interfaces of mobile phone applications (games & apps) and reponsive websites. Deliverables included research, interaction flow, wireframes, prototype and final visual design
- Handling projects from concept to production with project manager and developers
- App review and provide recommendations after launching apps to the marketplace

5.2013 - 12.2013

Multimedia Designer

Justsolve Consulting Limited



TOOLS

- Figma
- Sketch
- Axure RP9
- Invision
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- · Adobe After Effect
- Adobe InDesign

LANGUAGES

Cantonese

Mother Language

English

Basic Speaking Fluent Writing

Mandarin

Fluent

Andriod Mobile Game Apps, Responsive Web Interface

- Lead designer and work closely with engineers from conceptualization to final visual design
- Directly communicate and organise work milestone with client
- Deliverables included online & offline products: mobile applications user interfaces, flash animation, promotional materials (prints)

6.2012 - 5.2013

Multimedia Designer



Showcase (Kiosk) Interface, Web Interface

- Work closely with designers, programmers and project managers on mobile phone applications and digital showcases (Kiosk) interfaces, websites and offline marketing materials
- Various client projects including Hang Seng Bank, Sands Macau, Joint Publishing HK...etc

8.2009 - 6.2012

Senior Graphic Designer Fingerprint Limited

Graphic, Branding, Printing, Exhibition Material

- Print design and web design for marketing and branding services
- Communicate and organize the output process and timetable with clients
- Completing tasks by collaborating with junior colleagues

5.2008 - 7.2009

Graphic Designer Suncolor Limited

Graphic, Branding, Print Design Products

- Print design and web design for marketing and branding services.
- Printing composing and directly deal with clients' technical output problems



